<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.nolaowai.de"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
 <title>nolaowai.de</title>
 <link>http://www.nolaowai.de</link>
 <description></description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>About this website.</title>
 <link>http://www.nolaowai.de/?q=node/1</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-name-body field-type-text-with-summary field-label-hidden&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;field-item even&quot; property=&quot;content:encoded&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This web-site contains much of the writings of Stephen C. Van Wyck.  It is a &amp;quot;catch-basket&amp;quot; of various genres -- travel writing, living in Africa and China, poems, articles, educational curriculum material, and short stories.  It is an attempt to share one man&amp;#039;s writing with whoever might want to read it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     A number of factors have brought this web-site about: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     --I am a writer, and also a &amp;quot;pack-rat&amp;quot; (that is, I store away many things).  I like to observe the world around me, using &amp;quot;first-cut&amp;quot;, unedited prose.  I prefer to write by hand, or use primitive &amp;quot;word-processing&amp;quot; typewriters, rather than computers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     --I have lived a very varied and multi-lingual existence, and therefore had much to observe and write about. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     --It is very hard to &amp;quot;get published&amp;quot; at all, and almost impossible to get published on one&amp;#039;s own terms.  However, the Internet, and &amp;quot;blogs&amp;quot; and web-sites have given everyone a voice... even if it is only one small voice among thousands of others.  I do not chase fame, or money, but I do like the &amp;quot;power of distribution&amp;quot; -- the ability to reach many readers -- which the Internet is able to do. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     --I too have a voice, and I want to share what I have seen with others. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     Over the years, I have collected a lot of writing, which was not edited, put away in steel file-boxes, dated, and then left in the dark for many years.  As individual texts, it is not special, but taken as a whole, I feel there is something useful to share.  I do not believe that any publisher would publish this writing on my terms (that is, complete and &amp;quot;as it is&amp;quot;), so I have chosen to scan my typewritten and handwritten pages into &amp;quot;.pdf&amp;quot; files, and not re-type them as Word files.  Besides, I believe that the future of document transmission lies with &amp;quot;scanned&amp;quot; files, and and not &amp;quot;typed, alterable&amp;quot; files. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     The genres in this web-site are divided by category.  Follow the &amp;quot;Contents Page&amp;quot; to navigate your way around. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     Anyone can read, down-load, and share this.  No one can own it!  Please bear this in mind. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     If people from other countries want to translate certain parts of my writing into their language, that is fine.  The translated version (ie, T.L.) is yours.  I hope you will post it on your local web-site, with &amp;quot;links&amp;quot; to my web-site. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     It is my hope that many of the world&amp;#039;s forgotten, obscure, never-known writers (and artists and musicians) will find a small place in &amp;quot;cyber-space&amp;quot; to share their voice, under reasonable restraint, for others to find! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;     --April, 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2012 19:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>admin</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">1 at http://www.nolaowai.de</guid>
 <comments>http://www.nolaowai.de/?q=node/1#comments</comments>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
